

# SAFA AZZOUZ

As an engineer, I am actively pursuing a role as a full-stack developer. My extensive training in top-notch development methodologies, coupled with practical experience from diverse projects, has honed my skills in the latest technologies and frameworks that are currently in high demand. With my adaptable nature, motivation, and dynamic approach.

#### CONTACT



0636677771



safaazzouz1999@gmail.com

# LANGUAGE

- English
- Franche
- Arabe

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Programming languages: JAVA, kotlin, PHP, C,C++, JavaScript, CSS, HTML.
- Frameworks: Angular, Spring

  Boot, laravel, Drupal
- Operating system: Linux,
   Windows, Windows Server,
   Android
- Multimedia: Photoshop, Premiere
  Pro

# **EXPERIENCE**

# July 2022-September 2022

Two-month initiation internship within the service IT in National Office of Electricity and Drinking Water Laayoune

**Task**: develop a web application of management of trainees.

# **April 2021-June 2021**

Two-month technical internship in the service IT in the Urban agency of Laâyoune.

**Task**: develop a web application of office equipment management.

#### **EDUCATION**

2021 - 2024 Mohammedia

Software Engineering and Distributed Computing Systems - second year.

**Higher Normal School of Technical Education** 

2019 - 2021 Laayoune University Diploma of Technology in Computer Engineering

Laayoune Higher School of Technology